missamerica.org 2018-05-11

# Privacy Policy - Miss America

The Miss America Organization (the “Organization”) has created this statement to demonstrate its firm commitment to your privacy. The Organization does not collect personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. This policy is your guide as to how the Organization will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our website.

Throughout the Organization’s web pages, links may be provided to other servers which may contain information of interest to you. We take no responsibility for, and exercise no control over, the organizations, views, or accuracy of the information contained on such other servers. Creating a text link from your website to the Organization’s website does not require permission, provided such text link is provided consistent with law. If you have a link you would desire the Organization to consider adding to its website, please send an e-mail to info@missamerica.org with the subject “Link request.”

If you would like to publish information that you find on the Organization’s website, please send your request to info@missamerica.org. You are not permitted to use the Organization’s logo and images without the Organization’s consent to do so.

The Organization may collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet, the date and time you access our site, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked to our site. The Organization uses the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help the Organization make our site more useful to visitors.

If you complete the profile form and share your personally identifying information, this information will be used only to provide you with more targeted content. We may use your contact information to send further information about the Organization or to contact you when necessary. You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings, and how to do so is discussed below.

You also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment, or by filling out a web form that provides the Organization with this information. The Organization uses personal identifying information from e-mail primarily to respond to your requests. In so doing, the Organization may forward your e-mail to other employees who are better able to answer your questions. The Organization may also use your e-mail to contact you in the future about Organization programs that may be of interest.

The Organization will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. Except as might be required by law, the Organization will not share any information we receive with any outside parties.

If you sign up for one of the Organization’s e-mail lists, the Organization will only send you the kinds of information you have requested. The Organization will not share your name or e-mail address with any outside parties.

The Organization’s website provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us through a special online form. You may choose to receive only specific communications or none at all. You may also update your contact information previously provided to us through another online form. You cannot remove yourself from our database, but you can prevent unwanted communication.

The Organization truly values the privacy of its donors as well as those who visit our website. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website or your dealings with this website, you can contact the Organization at info@missamerica.org.
